moskart.com 2014-06-15

# Privacy Policy

Moskart.com highly values your privacy and ensures your online security seriously. In order to make you understand our policy fully, we provide the notice below to explain our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. If our Privacy Policy is updated, all revisions will be posted on this page. We reserve the right to update the privacy policy any time.

 **Information Collected**  
We collect your information in different ways on Moskart.com. One purpose for collecting personal information is to provide our customers with an efficient, meaningful, and customized online experience. For example, your personal information can be used to:  
* Help make this site easier for you to use by not having to enter information more than once.  
* Help you find information, products and services more quickly.  
* Help us create content on this site that is most relevant to you.  
* Help remind you of new information, products and services that we offer.  
At the same time, when you make a purchase from Moskart.com, we collect your name, email address, shipping and billing address(es), phone number and credit card number. Besides, we may also ask you for your gender and the country of your residence or your organization's country of operation so that we can comply with applicable laws and regulations. We collect this information in order to bill you for your order. We will not disclose your information to any third party, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

 **Information Use**  
Information collected may be used to enhance your shopping experience in the following ways:  
* Register to be a member of Moskart.com  
* Deliver products and services that you have purchased online  
* Prevent fraud and bill you for your purchases  
* Confirm your orders  
* Respond to your customer-service inquiries or requests  
* Introduce great valued and featured items to you  
* Find and stock the products you want  
* Customize your shopping experience

 **Security**  
Your personal information will be automatically encrypted or encoded before it is sent over the Internet by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL). When you enter Moskart.com, any personal information including address, telephone number, Social Security or EIN number, account number and other information that personally identifies you, is secured through data encryption technology. This protection applies in areas including but not limited to, online ordering, order status, and credit application. Any access to your personal information is restricted. Only employees who need access to this information to perform a specific job are granted the access to it. The site contains links to other web sites, and Moskart.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices on those third party web sites. You may need to review their respective privacy policies as well.

 **Cookies**  
Cookie technology can provide you with tailored information while visiting a Web site. Cookies are data elements that a Web site can send to your browser and are stored on your system. Some Web site pages use cookies to better serve you when you return to these Sites. The Site cookie sent to your address contains the country location you have selected and whether you have selected on-line settings for visiting the Site or not. The Site does not store individual names, email addresses, street addresses, credit card numbers or phone numbers in cookies placed on your computer. However, the Site does collect non-identifiable information from visits to our Site to help us provide better customer service. For example, we track the domains people visit and we measure visitors’ activities on the Site, but we do so in ways that keep personal information non-identifiable. Moskart.com uses this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service.

 **Updates to This Policy**  
If we change or update this Privacy Policy, we will post changes and updates on this Site so that you will always be aware of the latest information we collect, use and disclose. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy from time to time so that you know whether this Privacy Policy has been updated. If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy, please contact us.

 **Questions & Feedback**  
We welcome your questions, comments and concerns about our Policy. Please send us any feedback pertaining to privacy. For any other questions you can contact us.

 **Choice and Opt-Out**  
If you no longer wish to receive the promotional communications from Moskart.com, you may "opt-out" of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or contact us.
